[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "And then suddenly, out of nowhere, you get a call from this guy, front man of the Black Eyed Peas, one of the biggest pop stars in the world, music stars, what are you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "suddenly", ",", "out", "of", "nowhere", ",", "you", "get", "a", "call", "from", "this", "guy", ",", "front", "man", "of", "the", "Black", "Eyed", "Peas", ",", "one", "of", "the", "biggest", "pop", "stars", "in", "the", "world", ",", "music", "stars", ",", "what", "are", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "I didn't know what to think until I got on the phone and within one minute I thought I was in trouble, because the first thing he said to me was, Dean, I've heard you speak and I've heard you speak about your first program, which is about convincing kids that science and technology is critical to their future.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "think", "until", "I", "got", "on", "the", "phone", "and", "within", "one", "minute", "I", "thought", "I", "was", "in", "trouble", ",", "because", "the", "first", "thing", "he", "said", "to", "me", "was", ",", "Dean", ",", "I", "'ve", "heard", "you", "speak", "and", "I", "'ve", "heard", "you", "speak", "about", "your", "first", "program", ",", "which", "is", "about", "convincing", "kids", "that", "science", "and", "technology", "is", "critical", "to", "their", "future", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Black Eyed Peas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Is that the easiest way to describe?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "easiest", "way", "to", "describe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "That's a very good shorthand.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "shorthand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Oh, wholeheartedly.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "wholeheartedly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "So this amazing outfit you wore at the Super Bowl, which was this all-flashing, all-singing, all-dancing electronic super outfit, in fact the guy that designed the code for this was a graduate of the FIRST, originally, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "this", "amazing", "outfit", "you", "wore", "at", "the", "Super", "Bowl", ",", "which", "was", "this", "all-flashing", ",", "all-singing", ",", "all-dancing", "electronic", "super", "outfit", ",", "in", "fact", "the", "guy", "that", "designed", "the", "code", "for", "this", "was", "a", "graduate", "of", "the", "FIRST", ",", "originally", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "From England.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "England", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Does he have any involvement with this now, especially now you've got involved?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "have", "any", "involvement", "with", "this", "now", ",", "especially", "now", "you", "'ve", "got", "involved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "He makes an appearance on the show.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "makes", "an", "appearance", "on", "the", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "He does?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday", "August 14th"]}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "On Sunday?", "question_tokens": ["On", "Sunday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "On Sunday, August 14th.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "Sunday", ",", "August", "14th", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "VBG", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Is he playing with a robot or?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "playing", "with", "a", "robot", "or", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "No, just applauding and, you know, congratulating the kids and showing support for their discipline and hard work.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "just", "applauding", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "congratulating", "the", "kids", "and", "showing", "support", "for", "their", "discipline", "and", "hard", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "It's a question with \"Yes, We Can,\" has he?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "question", "with", "``", "Yes", ",", "We", "Can", ",", "''", "has", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "''", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "That wasn't a question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "n't", "a", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "To do your part to inspire someone to do their part?", "question_tokens": ["To", "do", "your", "part", "to", "inspire", "someone", "to", "do", "their", "part", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Interestingly, back in Britain at the moment, we've had a lot of riots this week.", "answer_tokens": ["Interestingly", ",", "back", "in", "Britain", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "we", "'ve", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "riots", "this", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "When you see what's going on with these riots and stuff, do you have an empathy with these kids or do you believe that actually the way out is to go another way?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "with", "these", "riots", "and", "stuff", ",", "do", "you", "have", "an", "empathy", "with", "these", "kids", "or", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "actually", "the", "way", "out", "is", "to", "go", "another", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "I remember the L.A. riot, the race riots in the early '90s.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "remember", "the", "L.A.", "riot", ",", "the", "race", "riots", "in", "the", "early", "'90s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "But I know they're part of your twisted mind, aren't they, Dean?", "question_tokens": ["But", "I", "know", "they", "'re", "part", "of", "your", "twisted", "mind", ",", "are", "n't", "they", ",", "Dean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "They are.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "You love these things, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "love", "these", "things", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "I love what they do for kids.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "what", "they", "do", "for", "kids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "This is the showoff entertainer but doesn't do very much, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "showoff", "entertainer", "but", "does", "n't", "do", "very", "much", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "This robot, you know that robot dance that we do?", "question_tokens": ["This", "robot", ",", "you", "know", "that", "robot", "dance", "that", "we", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "One of the kids built this or a team of kids?", "question_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "kids", "built", "this", "or", "a", "team", "of", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "A big kid built that.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "big", "kid", "built", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "This is the real brains one, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "real", "brains", "one", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "It was humiliating.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "humiliating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "It's not fully functional right now, but what can he do when he's going?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "fully", "functional", "right", "now", ",", "but", "what", "can", "he", "do", "when", "he", "'s", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, the goal of the robot -- every year we give the kids a different challenge.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "goal", "of", "the", "robot", "--", "every", "year", "we", "give", "the", "kids", "a", "different", "challenge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "How does it work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "They're remote-controlled.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "remote-controlled", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What do you think got you out?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "got", "you", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Encouragement.", "answer_tokens": ["Encouragement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Wright", "Ms. Montez"]}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "From who?", "question_tokens": ["From", "who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "My family, family friends, my teachers, Mr. Wright (ph), Ms. Montez (ph).", "answer_tokens": ["My", "family", ",", "family", "friends", ",", "my", "teachers", ",", "Mr.", "Wright", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "Ms.", "Montez", "(", "ph", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "When you see these gang kids, is a big part of the problem the fact they don't have anybody?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "these", "gang", "kids", ",", "is", "a", "big", "part", "of", "the", "problem", "the", "fact", "they", "do", "n't", "have", "anybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "No, but they do have somebody.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "they", "do", "have", "somebody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Can you achieve this kind of thing without the driving force of a mother or a father, somebody who is with you to be able to provide a chance to do it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "achieve", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "without", "the", "driving", "force", "of", "a", "mother", "or", "a", "father", ",", "somebody", "who", "is", "with", "you", "to", "be", "able", "to", "provide", "a", "chance", "to", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "ILL.I.AM: Well, it depends on the people around you.", "answer_tokens": ["ILL.I.AM", ":", "Well", ",", "it", "depends", "on", "the", "people", "around", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "And -- but yes, there's always ways out of it, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "--", "but", "yes", ",", "there", "'s", "always", "ways", "out", "of", "it", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "CC", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Your mother must be pretty proud of you.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "mother", "must", "be", "pretty", "proud", "of", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "How important is it to you to get somebody like him who, in one swoop, can basically get to millions and millions of kids in this country?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "it", "to", "you", "to", "get", "somebody", "like", "him", "who", ",", "in", "one", "swoop", ",", "can", "basically", "get", "to", "millions", "and", "millions", "of", "kids", "in", "this", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "You answered the question yourself.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "answered", "the", "question", "yourself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "What do you think of America as a business model right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "America", "as", "a", "business", "model", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "It goes over my head because I can't comprehend it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "goes", "over", "my", "head", "because", "I", "ca", "n't", "comprehend", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Dean, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Dean", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "AMEN: I agree, as usual, with Will.", "answer_tokens": ["AMEN", ":", "I", "agree", ",", "as", "usual", ",", "with", "Will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Should that be where America leads the field?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "that", "be", "where", "America", "leads", "the", "field", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "WRB", "NNP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Progress has always depended on innovation.", "answer_tokens": ["Progress", "has", "always", "depended", "on", "innovation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "That's a slight exaggeration.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "slight", "exaggeration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Was he a good baby sitter?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "a", "good", "baby", "sitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Again, not babysitter.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "not", "babysitter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Yes, yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Tom Cruise would be doing cartwheels?", "question_tokens": ["Tom", "Cruise", "would", "be", "doing", "cartwheels", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "No, like back flips.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "like", "back", "flips", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Oh yes, oh yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", ",", "oh", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Do you still see him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "see", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I do, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Has that been, on balance, a good thing or not a good thing for you?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "that", "been", ",", "on", "balance", ",", "a", "good", "thing", "or", "not", "a", "good", "thing", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I think -- personally, I think a really fortunate thing, because it exposed me to the business that I found myself in as an adult.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "personally", ",", "I", "think", "a", "really", "fortunate", "thing", ",", "because", "it", "exposed", "me", "to", "the", "business", "that", "I", "found", "myself", "in", "as", "an", "adult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 404, "question": "And the reason you're called Dallas is because?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "reason", "you", "'re", "called", "Dallas", "is", "because", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I was (INAUDIBLE) --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "And your siblings's middle names are?", "question_tokens": ["And", "your", "siblings", "'s", "middle", "names", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "My sisters are twins.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "sisters", "are", "twins", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Where do you get all of this information?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "all", "of", "this", "information", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "I've immersed myself in your life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "immersed", "myself", "in", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Do you ever get tempted?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "get", "tempted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Ever smoked?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "smoked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Any vices?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "vices", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Well, yeah, totally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yeah", ",", "totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Your vice is sugar?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "vice", "is", "sugar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What do you feel watching it now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "watching", "it", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "It was such an incredible thing that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "such", "an", "incredible", "thing", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 529, "question": "ORGAN: Are you worried about any controversy that this role will bring you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Are", "you", "worried", "about", "any", "controversy", "that", "this", "role", "will", "bring", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I haven't really thought about that, I mean, because it was a book first, and because --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "really", "thought", "about", "that", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "because", "it", "was", "a", "book", "first", ",", "and", "because", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "How many months pregnant are you now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "months", "pregnant", "are", "you", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I'm almost five months.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "almost", "five", "months", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "How is it all going?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "it", "all", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "It is -- it's amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "--", "it", "'s", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "ORGAN: Do you have any worries it may happen again?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "have", "any", "worries", "it", "may", "happen", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I mean I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Two actors together, with all of the, you know, insecurity that comes with acting, and the egos and all of the rest of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "actors", "together", ",", "with", "all", "of", "the", ",", "you", "know", ",", "insecurity", "that", "comes", "with", "acting", ",", "and", "the", "egos", "and", "all", "of", "the", "rest", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "The old man's got a few stashed away, hasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["The", "old", "man", "'s", "got", "a", "few", "stashed", "away", ",", "has", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "He's doing well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "doing", "well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Where does he keep them?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "he", "keep", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "In his office.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "his", "office", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Have you written the speech in your mind?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "written", "the", "speech", "in", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Who are you going to thank?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "you", "going", "to", "thank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Well, here's what would happen --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "'s", "what", "would", "happen", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "I mean, what a speech you've got ready to go, huh?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "a", "speech", "you", "'ve", "got", "ready", "to", "go", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Yeah, there's a lot of people to be grateful to.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "to", "be", "grateful", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]